<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications | Yingwen Zhang</title>
    <link>/publication/</link>
      <atom:link href="/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Publications</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 17:01:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/publication/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust beacon detection for fast-moving VLC systems: A learning method</title>
      <link>/publication/detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 17:01:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/detection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The main difference between our beacon detection task in VLC and other object detection tasks is that 
our target LEDs are fast-blinking in time domain, i.e., LEDs are modulated with information and the driving
current is changing with time. We tried to utilize this kind of temporal feature to distinguish beacon LEDs
from DC interferences and our solution is straight-forward: we first stacked multiple input frames into a RGB
image that converts the temporal information of LEDs into the spatial information of image. Then, using the advanced CNN object detector, we can 
detect the beacon candidate region with a very high recall in this stacked RGB map. 
Finally, given the coarse position information, a demodulator was designed to determine the &amp;lsquo;0/1&amp;rsquo; state of LEDs and once
beacons are coded with run-length coding, we can detect them robustly within 3 frames. Besides, we also proved that 
our detection framework can be easily generalized to inputs with more than 3 frames. The journal paper is drafted.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trajectory Prediction of Target Light Source for Dynamic Visible Light Communication Systems with A Narrow Field of View</title>
      <link>/publication/jiang/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 11:18:01 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/jiang/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Gain Control Design for Dynamic Visible Light Communication Systems</title>
      <link>/publication/agc-full-version/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2020 11:07:44 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/agc-full-version/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experimental investigation of dynamic visible light communication system with automatic gain control</title>
      <link>/publication/agc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 19:46:27 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/agc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
